Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Basil, Toni - Suspense, 1984; SR-11488; Basil, Toni (Box 183)
          Catalog # 4V9 42824; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42824-A-CP1
        - Bass 305 - Digital bass 2002, SR-11489; Bass 305 (Box 183)
          Catalog # DMR 41353; A-side Matrix # 25 DMR-41353-1A
          DM Records
          Pompano Beach, Florida
        - Bass City Rollaz - Everybody get funky, SR-11490; Bass City Rollaz (Box 183)
          Catalog # BCR003; A-side Matrix # BCR3A1
          Bass City Rollaz
        - BASS-FUNK-TION - Push the tempo - the remixes, 1995; SR-11491; BASS-FUNK-TION (Box 183)
          Catalog # FNR 004; A-side Matrix # FNR 004-A1
          Fat 'N Round
        - Bass FX - Makes u move, 2000; SR-12790; Bass FX; Carlucci, Dave (Box 183)
          Catalog # TMM-1583; A-side Matrix # TMM-1583-A
          Third Millennium Music
        - Bass Hit Crew - Who's gonna luv me; You give good love, 1994; SR-11492; Bass Hit Crew; Bright, Gina; King, Diana (Box 183)
          Catalog # CAS 6851; A-side Matrix # XSS-6851B-1A
        - Bass Injection - Separated, SR-11493; Bass Injection (Box 183)
          Catalog # INJECT1; A-side Matrix # INJECT1-A
        - Bass is Base - Floating, SR-11494; Bass is Base (Box 183)
          Catalog # PR12-7076-1-AS; A-side Matrix # PE12 7076-1AS-HS
          Loose Cannon
        - Bass is Base - Floating, SR-11495; Bass is Base (Box 183)
        - Bass Patrol - Do the alph, 1988; SR-11496; Bass Patrol (Box 183)
          Catalog # JB 5019; A-side Matrix # JB-5019-A-2
          Joey Boy Records
        - Bass Patrol - Your baby daddy got beef, SR-11497; Bass Patrol (Box 183)
          Catalog # JB 5052; A-side Matrix # JB-5052-A
        - Bass Patrol - The dirty bird, SR-11498; Bass Patrol (Box 183)
          Catalog # JB 5050; A-side Matrix # JB-5050-A
        - Bass Tech DJ - Bass the nation, 1994; SR-11499; Bass Tech DJ (Box 183)
          Catalog # PD-8850; A-side Matrix # PD-8850
          Pandisc Records
          Miami Beach, Florida
        - Bassbin Twins - EPIII, 1995; SR-11500; Bassbin Twins (Box 183)
          Catalog # BBT 03; A-side Matrix # BBT-3-A
        - Basscamp - Take your body, 1997; SR-11501; Basscamp (Box 183)
          Catalog # JCHEKT.103; A-side Matrix # JCHEKT 103 A
          Junior Cheeky Records
        - Bassface Sascha - The trumpet rmx; Fist funk, 1996; SR-11502; Bassface Sascha (Box 183)
          Catalog # KUS 17; A-side Matrix # KUS 12A-1
          Kickin' Underground Sound
        - Bassix - Tears of a clown; Fake 'n' move, 1987; SR-11503; Bassix (Box 183)
          Catalog # 49 06870; A-side Matrix # XSS176133-1A
        - Bass Kittens - Kittens ripped my flesh EP, 1995; SR-11505; Bass Kittens (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11506. 2 copies
          Catalog # OMWE-005; A-side Matrix # OMWE-005 ARE-1
          Oxygen Music Works
        - Bass Kittens - Kittens ripped my flesh EP, 1995; SR-11506; Bass Kittens (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11505. 2 copies
        - Bassomatic - Go getta nutha man, 1991; SR-11507; Bassomatic (Box 183)
          Catalog # GRRR18; A-side Matrix # GRRR 18-A-1J-1-1
          Guerilla
        - Bataan, Joe - Sadie (she smokes), 1980; SR-11508; Bataan, Joe (Box 183)
          Catalog # SG 330; A-side Matrix # SG330A
        - Bataan, Joe - Joe Bataan II, 1981; SR-11509; Bataan, Joe (Box 183)
          Catalog # SA 8549; A-side Matrix # SA8549-A
        - Bataan, Joe - Subway Joe, 1968; SR-11510; Bataan, Joe (Box 183)
          Catalog # SLP 345; A-side Matrix # 3972 SLP345-1
          Fania Records
        - Bataan, Joe - Young, gifted and brown, 2004; SR-11511; Bataan, Joe (Box 183)
          Catalog # VAMPI LP 062; A-side Matrix # 57008E1/A
          Vampi Soul
          Madrid, Spain
        - Battalion - Blacklisted; MC squared, 1999; SR-11512; Battalion; Arsonists; Anomolies (Box 183)
          Catalog # SUB 777; A-side Matrix # 25-SUB-777-1A
          Sub Records
        - Battlecat - On top of the world, 1995; SR-11513; Battlecat (Box 183)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7647; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7647-SR-1
          Maverick
        - Bautista, Roland - The heart of the wind, 1979; SR-11514; Bautista, Roland (Box 183)
          Catalog # AA-1071; A-side Matrix # AA-1071 A
          ABC Records
        - Baxter, Tony - Get up offa that thing (Godfather II), 1984; SR-11515; Baxter, Tony; Screamin' Tony Baxter (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11516. 2 copies
          Catalog # 12BRW 9; A-side Matrix # 12BRW 9A-2U-1X-1-1
          Fouth & Broadway
        - Baxter, Tony - Get up offa that thing (Godfather II), 1984; SR-11516; Baxter, Tony; Screamin' Tony Baxter (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11515. 2 copies
          Catalog # 12BRW 9; A-side Matrix # 12BRW 9A-1U1-1-1
        - Bazuka - Bazuka, 1975; SR-11517; Bazuka (Box 183)
          Catalog # SP-3406; A-side Matrix # A&M SP3411 P2
        - Bazuka, T.C. - Murphy's law; Dynomite, 1993; SR-11518; Bazuka, T.C.; Cheri (Box 183)
          Catalog # HCL 2246; A-side Matrix # HCL-2246-A
          Venture Records
        - BBJ - Pentecostal poppa, 1998; SR-11519; BBJ (Box 183)
          Catalog # INT8P 6510; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6510-A
          Blackstar Entertainment
        - B.E. Taylor Group - Vitamin L, 1983; SR-12791; B.E. Taylor Group (Box 183)
          Catalog # L33-1135; A-side Matrix # MCA-3645-AS4R-4
        - Beach Boys - L.A. (light album), 1979; SR-11520; Beach Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # JZ 35752; A-side Matrix # PAL-35752-10
          Caribou Records
        - Beach Boys - Happy endings, 1987; SR-11521; Beach Boys; Little Richard (Box 183)
          Catalog # B9392TP; A-side Matrix # B-9392-TP-A
          ATCO Records
        - BearEssense - The big hurt, 1983; SR-11522; BearEssense (Box 183)
          Catalog # BTG-1732; A-side Matrix # BTG 1732 A
          Moby Dick Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Beasley, Walter - On the edge; Where, 1987; SR-11523; Beasley, Walter (Box 183)
          Catalog # 887 413-1; A-side Matrix # 887413-1 AS SP1 1-1
        - Beasley, Walter - Back in love again, 1986; SR-11524; Beasley, Walter (Box 183)
          Catalog # ED 5166; A-side Matrix # STED 66840 A-1
        - Beasley, Walter - Where, 1987; SR-11525; Beasley, Walter (Box 183)
          Catalog # PRO 659-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 659-87 NP 7476 EDIT CBS G1
        - Beasley, Walter - On the edge, 1987; SR-11526; Beasley, Walter (Box 183)
        - Beasley, Watson - Don't let your chance go by, 1980; SR-11527; Beasley, Watson (Box 183)
          Catalog # PRO-A-871; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-871-AR1
        - Beastie Boys - Sure shot, 1994; SR-11528; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # SPRO-79412; A-side Matrix # SPRO 79412RE1-SR3
        - Beastie Boys - She's on it, 1985; SR-11529; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11530. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44-05292; A-side Matrix # XSS-174709-1A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Beastie Boys - She's on it, 1985; SR-11530; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          In same jacket as # SR-11529. 2 copies
        - Beastie Boys - An exciting evening at home with Shadrach, Meshach and Abednego, 2002; SR-11531; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # SMA 046; A-side Matrix # SMA-046
        - Beastie Boys - Cooky puss, 1983; SR-11532; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # MOTR26; A-side Matrix # MOTR-26-A
          Rat Cage Records
        - Beastie Boys - Scientists of sound; The blow up factor, 1991; SR-11533; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # GR071; A-side Matrix # GR-071
          Grand Royal
        - Beastie Boys - Love American style EP, 1998; SR-11534; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # GR 064; A-side Matrix # GR064-A
        - Beastie Boys - Get it together, 1994; SR-11535; Beastie Boys (Box 183)
          Catalog # SPRO 79269; A-side Matrix # SPRO 79369 32 S-29432 X
        - Beastie Boys - Ch-check it out; Jump (breaks remix), 2004; SR-11536; Beastie Boys; Van Halen (Box 183)
          Catalog # BOYO1; A-side Matrix # BOYO1A
        - Beastie Boys - Ch-check it out; Jump (breaks remix), 2004; SR-11537; Beastie Boys; Van Halen (Box 184)
        - Beastie Boys - Paul's boutique, 1989; SR-11538; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          Catalog # C1-91743; A-side Matrix # C1-1-91743-Z1
          Beastie Boys Records
        - Beastie Boys - Intergalactic, 1998; SR-11539; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          Catalog # 7087 6 12872 1 9; A-side Matrix # SPRO-12872-A
        - Beastie Boys - Licensed to ill, 1986; SR-11540; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          Catalog # C 40238; A-side Matrix # AL-40238-1A-B
        - Beastie Boys - Hold it, now hit it, 1986; SR-11541; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11542. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44-05369; A-side Matrix # XSS-175033-2A
        - Beastie Boys - Hold it, now hit it, 1986; SR-11542; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11541. 2 copies
        - Beastie Boys - It's the new style; Paul Revere, 1986; SR-11543; Beastie Boys (Box 184)
          Catalog # 44-05958; A-side Matrix # XSS-175424-1A
        - Bomb the Bass - Beat dis, 1988; SR-11544; Bomb the Bass (Box 184)
          Catalog # B.C. 12-2093-40; A-side Matrix # DM C-1429 A-1/2-88
          BCM Records
        - Bomb the Bass - Beat dis, 1988; SR-11545; Bomb the Bass (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11546. Different discs
          Catalog # B.C. 12-2093-40R; A-side Matrix # DM C-1511 A-1/2-88
        - Bomb the Bass - Beat dis (remix), 1988; SR-11546; Bomb the Bass (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11545. Different discs
          Catalog # D00D R121; A-side Matrix # D00D-R-12-1 A-1
          Mister-Ron Records
        - Beat Junkies - Changes; Materialize, 1998; SR-11547; Beat Junkies (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11548. Different discs
          Catalog # SMR 36; A-side Matrix # SMR 36A
          Second Movement Recordings
        - Area 51 - Aqua funk; Crossfade, 1999; SR-11548; Area 51 (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11547. Different discs
          Catalog # PROMO 26; A-side Matrix # 12PROMO-26-A1
          Promo Recordings
        - Beat Kids - Open rhythm system (Disc one), 2003; SR-11549; Beat Kids (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11551. Double album
          Catalog # UJR-005-1; A-side Matrix # UJR005-1 ARE
          Uncle Junior Records
        - Beat Kids - Open rhythm system (Disc two), 2003; SR-11550; Beat Kids (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11550. Double album
          Catalog # UJR-005-1; A-side Matrix # UJR005-1 CRE
        - Beatles - Sgt. Pepper's lonely hearts club band, 1977; SR-13313; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # 1 C 072-04 177; A-side Matrix # 04177-A1
        - Beatles - Abbey Road, 1981; SR-13314; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # 1 C 072-04 243; A-side Matrix # 1042431-A1
        - Beatles - The Beatles at the Hollywood bowl, 1977; SR-11551; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # EMTV 4; A-side Matrix # 062-06377-A--31779-2Y
          Parlophone
        - Beatles - Rarities, 1979; SR-11552; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # 1 C 038-06 867; A-side Matrix # 06867-A2
          EMI Electrola
        - Beatles - Please please me, 1977; SR-11553; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # 1 C 072-04 219; A-side Matrix # 04219-A2
        - Beatles - Magical mystery tour, 1981; SR-11554; Beatles (Box 184)
          Catalog # 1 C 072-04 449; A-side Matrix # 04449-A1+C
        - Beatmaster - Lipservice, 1984; SR-11555; Beatmaster (Box 184)
          Catalog # TB 842; A-side Matrix # TB-842-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Beat Master Clay D - Rock the house, 1988; SR-11556; Beat Master Clay D; D.J. Magic Mike (Box 184)
          Catalog # VR 1202; A-side Matrix # VR-1202-A
          Vision Records
        - Beat Master Clay D - Get it girl, 1990; SR-11557; Beat Master Clay D; Prince Rahiem (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11558. 2 copies
          Catalog # VR-1246; A-side Matrix # VR-1246-A
        - Beat Master Clay D - Get it girl, 1990; SR-11558; Beat Master Clay D; Prince Rahiem (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11557. 2 copies
        - Beatmasters - Rock da house (remix), 1988; SR-11559; Beatmasters (Box 184)
          Catalog # LEFT S11T; A-side Matrix # LEFT 11T AL
          Rhythm King Records
        - Beatmasters - Rock da house (remix), 1988; SR-11560; Beatmasters (Box 184)
        - Beatnuts - No escapin' this, 2000; SR-11561; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          Catalog # RPROLP 4473; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-4473 A
          Loud Records
        - Beatnuts - Se acabo (translated remix), 1999; SR-11562; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11563. 2 copies
          Catalog # RPROLP4316; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-4316A
        - Beatnuts - Se acabo (translated remix), 1999; SR-11563; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11562. 2 copies
        - Beatnuts - Stone crazy album sampler, 1997; SR-11564; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          Catalog # XPR 3148; A-side Matrix # 31 3148 20 1A1
          Relativity
        - Beatnuts - Se acabo (translated remix), 1999; SR-11565; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          Catalog # RPROLP4316; A-side Matrix # RPROLP 4316A
        - Beatnuts - We got the funk, 2002; SR-11566; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11567. 2 copies
          Catalog # 9145-1; A-side Matrix # RPROLP4571A
        - Beatnuts - We got the funk, 2002; SR-11567; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11566. 2 copies
        - Beatnuts - No escapin' this, 2001; SR-11568; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11569. 2 copies
          Catalog # 6713416; A-side Matrix # 671341A
        - Beatnuts - No escapin' this, 2001; SR-11569; Beatnuts (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11568. 2 copies
        - Beats International - Dub be good to me, 1990; SR-11570; Beats International (Box 184)
          Catalog # ED 5431; A-side Matrix # STED 66654 A-1
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Beats International - Won't talk about it, 1990; SR-11571; Beats International (Box 184)
          Catalog # GOD X 43; A-side Matrix # GODX 43 A-1U-1-2
          Go! Beat
        - Beats International - Change your mind, 1992; SR-11572; Beats International (Box 184)
          Catalog # 869 709-1; A-side Matrix # 869-709-1 A RE-SP1
        - Beatty, Ethel - I know you care, 1981; SR-11573; Beatty, Ethel (Box 184)
          Catalog # UMD 7012; A-side Matrix # PA-007A
          Uno Melodic Records
        - Beautiful People - Rilly Groovy, 1993; SR-11574; Beautiful People; Hendrix, Jimi (Box 184)
          Catalog # 12315-1; A-side Matrix # 12315-0A
          Continuum Records
          Cranford, New Jersey
        - Beauvoir, Jean - Feel the heat, 1986; SR-11575; Beauvoir, Jean (Box 184)
          Catalog # 44-05387; A-side Matrix # XSS-175125-1A
        - Beauvoir, Jean - Jimmy, 1988; SR-11576; Beauvoir, Jean (Box 184)
          Catalog # 44 07585; A-side Matrix # XSS-177651 1A
        - Beck - Where it's at, 1996; SR-11577; Beck (Box 184)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4875; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4875-A-GL1
          Geffen Records, Inc
        - Beck, Floyd - Party is the solution, 1980; SR-13315; Beck, Floyd (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-13316. 2 copies
          Catalog # AS 867; A-side Matrix # AA-XSS-167809-A
          Precison
        - Beck, Floyd - Party is the solution, 1980; SR-13316; Beck, Floyd (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-13315. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Beck, Jeff - Live, 1977; SR-11578; Beck, Jeff; Jan Hammer Group (Box 184)
          Catalog # PE 34433; A-side Matrix # AL 34433-1H
        - Beck, Kenny - $ucce$$ i$ the word, 1985; SR-11579; Beck, Kenny; 12:41 (Box 184)
          Catalog # FRE-004; A-side Matrix # FRE-004XA
          Fresh Records
        - Beck, Robin - Sweet Talk, 1979; SR-11580; Beck, Robin (Box 184)
          Catalog # MK-111; A-side Matrix # MK-111B1-1-1
        - Becket - Celebration, 1985; SR-11581; Becket (Box 184)
          Catalog # PC 21; A-side Matrix # PC-21-A
          Cocoa Records
        - Becket - Love is the answer, 1984; SR-11582; Becket (Box 184)
          Catalog # PL 12; A-side Matrix # PL-12-A-2-RE
        - Becket - The tickle; Screws, 1989; SR-11583; Becket (Box 184)
          Catalog # TS 89-31-12; A-side Matrix # PTS-31-89-12 A
        - Becket - Yuh sweet, 1987; SR-11584; Becket (Box 184)
          Catalog # PYS 0080; A-side Matrix # PYS-0080-A1
        - Bee Gees - E•S•P, 1987; SR-11585; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          Catalog # 925 541-1; A-side Matrix # 1-25544-A-INTL-DMM-1
        - Bee Gees - E•S•P, 1987; SR-11586; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2918; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2918-DMM-SH1
        - Bee Gees - Here at last - live (Disc one), 1977; SR-11587; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11588. Double album
          Catalog # 2479-188 A; A-side Matrix # 2479 1 88 A
          RSO
        - Bee Gees - Here at last - live (Disc two), 1977; SR-11588; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11587. Double album
          Catalog # 2479-188 A; A-side Matrix # 2479 1 89 B
        - Bee Gees - Spirits having flown, 1979; SR-11589; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11590. 2 copies
          Catalog # RS-1-3041; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3041-AS-REV-1-RM2
        - Bee Gees - Spirits having flown, 1979; SR-11590; Bee Gees (Box 184)
          In same jacket as # SR-11589. 2 copies
        - Bee, Jay - A-classic, SR-11591; Bee, Jay (Box 184)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 08 42042 20 1A1 PULSE 001
          Pulse Recordings
        - Bad Bascomb - Black grass music, 1973; SR-11592; Bad Bascomb (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11593. 2 copies
          Catalog # PAS-6048; A-side Matrix # PAS-6048-A
          Paramount
        - Bad Bascomb - Black grass music, 1973; SR-11593; Bad Bascomb (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11592. 2 copies
        - Bee, Kenny - Dance all night (till you get it right), 1980; SR-11594; Bee, Kenny (Box 185)
          Catalog # SM 12-404; A-side Matrix # SM-12-404-A
          SMI Records
        - Bee Why - Reality, 1997; SR-11595; Bee Why; B. Stacey (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11596. 2 copies
          Catalog # WPK003; A-side Matrix # WPK-003-A
          Wolfpak
        - Bee Why - Reality, 1997; SR-11596; Bee Why; B. Stacey (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11595. 2 copies
        - Beenie Man - Blessed, 1995; SR-11597; Beenie Man (Box 185)
          Catalog # 162-539 950-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-950-1-AS/HS
          Island Jamaica
        - Beenie Man - Bad man bizness; Video, 2001; SR-11598; Beenie Man; India.Arie; Supercat (Box 185)
          Catalog # UNIR 20622-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20622-1A
        - Beenie Man - Dude remixes, 2004; SR-11185; Beenie Man (Box 185)
          Catalog # 7243 8 38919 1 7; A-side Matrix # 07243-838919-1-7 A
          Virgin Records America
        - Beenie Man - Love me now, 2000; SR-11186; Beenie Man (Box 185)
          Catalog # 7087-6-14935-1-1; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-14935-1-1 RE1-A
        - Beenie Man - Feel it boy, 2002; SR-11187; Beenie Man; Janet (Box 185)
          Catalog # 7243 8 38846 1 2; A-side Matrix # 7248-8-38846-1 2 A
        - Beenie Man - Slam, 1995; SR-11188; Beenie Man (Box 185)
          Catalog # 162-537 872-1; A-side Matrix # 162-537-872-2-A
        - Beenie Man - Memories, 1995; SR-11189; Beenie Man; Buddha Stretch (Box 185)
          Catalog # VPRL 5881; A-side Matrix # VPRO 5881-A
          Fat Eyes Records
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Beezel - See about ya, 2003; SR-11190; Beezel; Bone Crusher; Banner, David (Box 185)
          Catalog # DEFR 15984-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15984-1A
          Def Jam South
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Beezel - See about ya, 2003; SR-11191; Beezel; Bone Crusher; Banner, David (Box 185)
        - Before Dark - Come correct, 1998; SR-11192; Before Dark (Box 185)
          Catalog # RDAA-65599-1; A-side Matrix # RDAA-65599-1-A-1
        - Began Began - Computer wars, 1982; SR-11193; Began Began (Box 185)
          Catalog # OW-005; A-side Matrix # OW-005-A
          One Way Records
        - Begg, Si - Network Southeast Volume 2, 2000; SR-11194; Begg, Si (Box 185)
          Catalog # UNDER 14; A-side Matrix # UNDER 14 A-01-1
          Under 5's
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Belafonte - An evening with Belafonte/Makeba, 1965; SR-11195; Belafonte; Makeba (Box 185)
          Catalog # LPM 3420; A-side Matrix # R 3RM-4386--2S A2
          RCA Victor
        - Belafonte - An evening with Belafonte/Makeba, 1965; SR-11196; Belafonte; Makeba (Box 185)
          Catalog # LPM 3420; A-side Matrix # R 3RM-4386--1S
        - Belgium Hip Hop Squad - Phat unda compil, 1997; SR-11197; Belgium Hip Hop Squad (Box 185)
          Catalog # CNN199; A-side Matrix # CNN 199-A1
          Souterrain Productions
          Belgium
        - Bell & James - Shakedown, 1979; SR-11198; Bell & James (Box 185)
          Catalog # SP-17104; A-side Matrix # AMSP012029A-SM3
          A&M Disco
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Poison, 1990; SR-11199; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11200. Different discs
          Catalog # L33-18219; A-side Matrix # MCA-9813 FDS-1
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Poison, 1990; SR-11200; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11199. Different discs
          Catalog # MCA-24003; A-side Matrix # MCA-9596 FDS-1
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Above the rim, 1993; SR-11201; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11202. Different discs
          Catalog # MCA8P 2624; A-side Matrix # MCA-11690-HF1
        - Breakdown - Oooh… that's my song, 1995; SR-11202; Breakdown (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11201. Different discs
          Catalog # 72392 78039-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 78039 1A
          Scotti Bros Records
        - Bell Biv Devoe - When will I see you smile again?, 1990; SR-11203; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          Catalog # L33-1172; A-side Matrix # MCA 10484 FOS-1
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Above the rim, 1993; SR-11204; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Da hot sh** (aight), 2001; SR-11205; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          Catalog # 440 015 384-1; A-side Matrix # 440-015-384-1A-RE1
        - Bell Biv Devoe - B.B.D. (I thought it was me)?, 1990; SR-11206; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          Catalog # MCA12 53899; A-side Matrix # MCA-10303 FDS-1
        - Bell Biv Devoe - Above the rim, 1993; SR-11207; Bell Biv Devoe (Box 185)
          Catalog # MCA8P 2624; A-side Matrix # MCA-11690-HF2
        - Bell, Jenny - Love don't live here no more, SR-11208; Bell, Jenny (Box 185)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # SOUL 5A
        - Bell, Jerry - Winter love affair, 1981; SR-11209; Bell, Jerry (Box 185)
          Catalog # MCA-5180; A-side Matrix # MCA-2503 W1
        - Bell, Nayanka - Amino, 1984; SR-11210; Bell, Nayanka (Box 185)
          Catalog # MSA 10101; A-side Matrix # 10101 A
          Media Show Africa
        - Belle, Regina - Show me the way, 1987; SR-12792; Belle, Regina (Box 185)
          Catalog # 44-06782; A-side Matrix # XSS175971-1A
        - Belle, Regina - Don't let go, 1998; SR-11211; Belle, Regina (Box 185)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4235; A-side Matrix # MCA 13258
        - Belle Stars - The belle stars, 1983; SR-11212; Belle Stars (Box 185)
          Catalog # 1-23866; A-side Matrix # B-17875-SH1
        - Belle Stars - World domination, 1986; SR-11213; Belle Stars (Box 185)
          Catalog # MCA-23671; A-side Matrix # MCA 6065 SS3
        - Belle Stars - Sign of the times, 1983; SR-11214; Belle Stars (Box 185)